Hi what can I get for you today?
Is this true?
(One of the top ten greatest American dining experience) Yeah
Right can I take your orders?
Ah.
I will have a banana split with extra cherries...
Some blueberry pancakes...
and a hot chocolate with cream.
Ha-ha you're hungry.
He-he-ha and a extra fucking spoon.
Excuse me?
For him.
Ok so you can't use language like that.
otherwise I'm going to have to ask you and your boyfriend to leave.
Ok.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
(Sigh)
I will have a great big banana shit...
with extra fucking cherries on top of it.
Ok sorry that's it. Right.
Marvin!
Oh yeah go get Marvin.
See if Marvin can make a banana split for me
You fucking cunt.
Bye Marvin!